Guide to the Burton Hall Papers WAG.087
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Burton Hall Papers
1943-2004
1960-1995
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Hall, Burton
Dieterich, Harriet
Sloan, Wendy
WAG.087
75 Linear Feet in 73 record cartons, 3 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box, and 3 folders.
Burton Hall was an attorney in New York who set up practice in 1960 as a labor lawyer. He began by handling a union insurgency case which then led to others, so that his practice was almost entirely comprised of representing rank-and-file members suing to protect their democratic rights within their unions. The collection principally consists of legal case files, including affidavits, depositions, motions, District Court and appellate briefs, exhibits, appendices, transcripts and correspondence. The collection provides a wealth of information about the politics and culture of rank-and-file organizing.
Custodial History
The records of Burton Hall were transferred from the office of Hall & Sloan at 401 Broadway, New York City, to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives in two installments in the summer of 1992. The records were donated by agreement with the Executor for the Estate of Burton Hall, Ellen Winner, Esq. of Rabinowitz, Boudin, Standard, Krinsky, & Lieberman, and in agreement with his family (sister Harriet Hall Dieterich and brother Henry P. Hall). An accretion to the records was transferred to the Wagner Labor Archives, in agreement with Wendy Sloan, Esq., (former) partner of Burton Hall, in 2007-2008.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Biographical Note
Burton Hall (1929-1991) was born in South Orange, New Jersey in 1929. He graduated from Williams College in 1951 and Yale Law School in 1954. While in college and law school, Hall was a member of the Food, Tobacco and Agricultural Workers Union in Camden, New Jersey, the International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Local 11, and the International Association of Machinists, Local 751, on the West Coast. He served in the U.S. Army from 1954 to 1956. He was admitted to the New York bar in 1957 and worked as a lawyer for a private firm and the Federal Aviation Agency before turning to labor law.
Hall set up his own practice in 1960 as a labor lawyer. Unintentionally at first, he found himself handling a union insurgency case which then led to others, so that his practice was almost entirely comprised of representing rank-and-file members suing to protect their democratic rights within their unions.
His office was located at 136 Liberty Street in Lower Manhattan. When the building was demolished to make way for the World Trade Center, he moved to 401 Broadway. His firm, Hall, Clifton & Schwartz, formed in 1980. Wendy Sloan became an associate in 1982 and the firm of Hall & Sloan was formed in 1984.
Hall was one of the pioneer attorneys in developing the case law for the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, also known as the Landrum-Griffin Act. His precedent-setting cases involved protection of the rights guaranteed by law in the section of the Act known as the "Bill of Rights" of union members. For instance, in Salzhandler v. Caputo, one of the earliest of the many disciplinary cases litigated by Hall for members of the Painters' Union, Hall articulated the right of free speech in unions in broad and unequivocal terms. Salzhandler was the first of many landmark cases which established legal protection for the rights of union members. Hall represented rank-and-filers in numerous cases involving issues such as eligibility for running for union office, discipline against members for criticism of their leadership, and expulsion of union members for advocating radical political ideas.
Burton Hall died in 1991 at age 61.
Bibliography:
Autocracy and Insurgency in Organized Labor. ed. Burton H. Hall. (New Brunswick: Transaction Books, 1972).
Benson, H. W. Democratic Rights for Union Members: A Guide to Internal Union Democracy. (New York: Association for Union Democracy, 1979).
Benson, Herman. "Insurgency and Reform in the Painters: 1960-1987." (unpublished paper at Wagner Labor Archives).
Cook, Alice H. Union Democracy: Practice and Ideal. (Ithaca: Cornell, 1963).
Corruption and Racketeering in the New York City Construction Industry. Interim Report by the New York State Organized Crime Task Force. (Ithaca: ILR Press, 1988).
Corruption and Racketeering in the New York City Construction Industry. Final Report to Governor Mario M. Cuomo. Ronald Goldstock, Director, New York State Organized Crime Task Force. December, 1989.
Crowe, Kenneth C. Collision: How The Rank And File Took Back The Teamsters. (New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1993).
The Edge: Organized Crime, Business, and Labor Unions. President's Commission on Organized Crime. Report to the President and the Attorney General. (Washington: GPO, Oct. 1985).
Frank, Miriam. "New York City's Carpenters Unions - The Status of Union Democracy." (1988: unpublished paper at Wagner Labor Archives).
Fink, Leon and Greenberg, Brian. Upheaval in the Quiet Zone: A History of Hospital Workers Union, Local 1199. (Urbana: University of Illinois Press, 1989).
Freeman, Joshua B. In Transit: The Transport Workers Union in New York City, 1933-1966. (New York: Oxford University Press, 1989).
Hutchinson, John. The Imperfect Union: A History of Corruption in American Trade Unions. (New York: E.P. Dutton, 1972).
McLaughlin, Doris B. and Shoomaker, Anita. The Landrum-Griffin Act and Union Democracy. (University of Michigan Press, 1979).
Summers, Clyde W. Democracy In A One-Party State. Maryland Law Review, Inc. Vol. 43, Number 1, 1984).
Summers, Clyde W. and Rabin, Robert J. The Rights of Union Members. ACLU Handbook. 1979.
Summers, Clyde W., Rauh, Joseph L., Benson, Herman. Union Democracy and Landrum-Griffin. Association for Union Democracy, 1986.
Taft, Philip. Corruption and Racketeering in the Labor Movement. (Ithaca: ILR Press, 1958).
Waldinger, Roger, and Bailey, Thomas. "The Continuing Significance of Race: Racial Conflict and Racial Discrimination in Construction." (Published Paper, Conservation of Human Resources, Columbia University, January, 1991).
Waldinger, Roger D. Through the Eye of the Needle: Immigrants and Enterprise in New York's Garment Trades. (New York: NYU Press, 1986)
Zausner, Philip. Unvarnished: The Autobiography of a Labor Leader. (New York: Brotherhood Publishers, 1941).
Scope and Content Note
This collection documents approximately thirty years of the union democracy movement, from the 1960s to the 1990s. It provides an opportunity to examine the development of a significant portion of the case law which gave meaning and substance to the rights guaranteed by the Landrum-Griffin Act, also known as the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959. The legal records, include affidavits, depositions, motions, District Court and appellate briefs, exhibits, appendices, transcripts, and correspondence. These materials provide a wealth of information about the politics and culture of rank-and-file organizing in general and rank-and-file organizing within specific unions. Additionally, the newspapers, flyers, programs, platforms, campaign literature, reports, annotated minutes, correspondence, and a small number of photographs provide a rich data base for documenting the vital sub-culture of union insurgents, as many of the cases stemmed from an individual who was part of some organized opposition group.
Of particular note is the correspondence found in the collection. Burton Hall maintained a lively correspondence with those he represented. The letters from John Cole, Seafarer (Cole v. Paul Hall, SIU); Harold Robbins, Painter, District Council 9 (former bodyguard to Trotsky); and those to the plaintiffs in Gordon v. Winpisinger (IAM) are outstanding examples. The collection contains a vast amount of correspondence wherein Hall would lay out a legal argument, either to a Judge sitting on one of his cases, to the opposing Counsel, or to one of the many attorneys who wrote seeking his expert advice, or copies of his briefs.
Arrangement
The Burton Hall Papers are arranged into five series.
Series I: Burton Hall - General
Series II: Union Democracy Cases
Series II: Employment Discrimination
Series IV: Photographs
Series V: 2007-2008 Accretions
Series I to Series IV are arranged alphabetically by subject/author heading or chronologically depending on the nature of the series.
Series V has not been arranged by an archivist. The order in which these materials were sent to the Tamiment Library has been maintained.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Burton Hall Union Democracy Oral History Project (OH 034)
Frank Schonfeld Papers (WAG 027)
Frank Schonfeld Photographs (DC9 Painters - IBPAT) (PHOTOS 144)
Daniel French Papers (WAG 101)
Carl Blum Papers (WAG 100)
Autocracy and Insurgency in Organized Labor by Burton Hall (HD6508.H24)
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Estate of Burton Hall and in agreement with his family (sister Harriet Hall Dieterich, brother Henry P. Hall, and former partner Wendy Sloan) in 1992. An accretion to the records was donated in agreement with Wendy Sloan, Esq. in 2007-2008. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 1992.015 and 1992.016.
Briefs (legal documents); Labor unions -- Stevedores -- New York (State); Labor unions -- Construction workers -- New York (State); Labor union democracy -- New York (State); Labor unions and the arts -- New York (State); Labor laws and legislation -- New York (State); Correspondence.; New York (State); Labor unions -- Corrupt practices -- New York (State); Transport workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- New York (State); Photographs.; Transcripts.; Depositions.; Affidavits.; Legal documents.; Lawyers -- New York (State); Collective labor agreements -- Lawyers.; National Labor Law Center (U.S.); American Civil Liberties Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Stablemen, and Helpers of America; United States. Federal Aviation Administration; Hall, Burton; Dieterich, Harriet; Sloan, Wendy
- Series I: Burton Hall - General
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I contains fragmentary files of the various organizations that Hall was active in, such as the Workers Defense League and the Committee for the Defense of Soviet Political Prisoners. There is also some correspondence, writings, and materials pertaining to specific cases.
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - D. McLaughlin / Department of Labor Study, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Collected Writings, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Obituaries, biography, etc., 1991, undated (Box 1, Folder 3a)
  - American Civil Liberties Union/New York, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Association for Union Democracy/Labor Democracy Foundation, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee for the Defense of Soviet Political Prisoners, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National Labor Law Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - New Politics Foundation, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Transaction Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fund for Human Rights Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Workers Defense League - Matteawan State Hospital, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Workers Defense League - Amicus, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lawyers Committee for International Human Rights, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Viet Nam Protest 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Attorneys Fees, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings (Union Democracy, B. Hall), undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Boilermakers, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Carpenters, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18a)
  - Drug, Hospital and Healthcare Employees, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Furniture & Piano Moving, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ironworkers, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Machinists (IAM), undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Miners (UMWA), undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Painters, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Papermakers, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Steelworkers, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26a)
  - Theatrical & Stage Employees (IATSE), undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - United Auto Workers, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - World's Fair Picketing, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board of Education, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Smith Act (Telford Taylor), undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Arthur Kinoy v District of Columbia, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Perez-Varella/Reissner v Rogers, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hall, Clifton & Schwartz, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Research, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Series II: Union Democracy Cases
  Scope and Content Note
  The division of Series II into subseries highlights the fact that certain sectors of the labor movement generated a large proportion of the individuals seeking legal representation in union democracy cases. Burton Hall served as an advisor to efforts to reform the International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT) from its earliest days, and this series documents his contributions to the Professional Drivers Council (PROD), Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU), and F.O.R.E. (Fear of Reprisal Ends). The correspondence between principals such as Steve Early (PROD), Arthur Fox (PROD), and Ken Paff (TDU) is especially interesting for its consideration of strategies. Of the numerous cases represented in the collection (filed numerically by Local), interest centers on the myriad manipulations of the members and the response to these manipulations at the international level.
  This series also richly documents significant cases within the construction trades. Certain of the Teamster locals fall within this category as well, such as Local 272 of the IBT. The Interim Report on "Corruption and Racketeering in the NYC Construction Industry," cited in the bibliography, is replete with references to cases litigated by Hall (Carpenters, Laborers, Steamfitters, Housewreckers, IBT Local 272).
  The seafaring unions provided another disproportionate share of clients. Both East and West Coast Longshoremen were represented by Burton Hall, and the jurisdictional tangles between the various seafaring unions represented in the collection provides an inside look at the "maritime jungle." Their "robust unionism" is well represented in the vast amount of literature and correspondence produced in the course of their struggles.
  There are also legal case files from unions in the transportation and entertainment industries, particularly the Transport Workers Union (TWU); the International Association of Machinists (IAM); the American Federation of Musicians (AFM); the International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Operators (IATSE); and National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET). Additionally, cases involving the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU); the National Union of Hospital & Health Care Employees, District 1199; and numerous other unions are also present in this series.
  - Subseries A: International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT)
    - Local 111, American Communications Association, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Local 138; Associated Food Inc., undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Local 138; Classic Truck Rental Corp. - 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Local 138; Classic Truck Rental Corp. - 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Local 138; Classic Truck Rental Corp. - 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Local 138; Classic Truck Rental Corp. - 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Local 138; White Rose Foods Corp., undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Local 210; Janovic Plaza, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Local 237, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Local 282 - Jo-San Asphalt Haulers Inc., 1974; Columbia Asphalt, 1978, 1974, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Local 282 - Kuebler, J., Willets Point Contracting Corp., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Local 282 - Katsaros, T. Curd, C., 1977; Szostak, M., 1978-79, 1977, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Local 282 - General Contractors Ass. of N.Y. v. IBT Local 282, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Local 282 - Curd, C. Katsaros, T., Kudla, L., Kuebler, J. - Trial Transcript, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Local 282 - Kuebler, E., Thomas H. Gannon & Sons, Inc., 1979- 80 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Local 282 - Frank Mascali Const. Co., 1979-84, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Local 282 - Kudla, W., Transit-Mix, 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Local 282 - O & T Transit-Mix, 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Local 282 - NLRB Charges, News Clippings, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Local 282 - F.O.R.E. (Fear of Reprisals Ends), undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Local 445 - McLean Trucking Co., undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Local 456 - 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Local 560 - Indictment4, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Local 617 - Hart, M., Hudson Jersey Sanitation, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Local 707, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Local 732 - Airline & Aerospace Employees/J.F. Kennedy Airport, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Local 803, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Local 807, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Local 807 - Merger with Local 820/Brinks 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Local 807 - Brinks, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Local 807 - Brinks, 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Local 807 - Brinks, Bargaining Agreements, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Local 807 - Joseph Whelan Trucking, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Local 807 - Joseph Whelan, etc., 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Local 802, IBT; Paramount Wire Co., 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Local 814; Neptune Worldwide Moving, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Local 814, 1977; 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Local 816; Streichler Trucking, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Local 816; Appellant's Brief, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Local 819, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Local 831 - NY City Sanitationmen, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Local 966; Lewis Frey Sales Corp., undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - IBT - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - TDU (Teamsters for a Democratic Union), undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - PROD (Professional Drivers Council), undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - PROD; Civil Action 76-0638, etc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - PROD; Fitzsimmons Removal Effort, 1977-79, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - PROD; Burt Hall - NLRB Charges, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - PROD; "The Van Brunt Stage", undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - PROD; US Labor Party (v PROD), undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Subseries B: Construction
    - United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners
      - Wayfield, David, et. al. v. Babcock, George, Secretary- Treasurer, Local 1837, District Council of Carpenters, Nassau County; 63 Civ. 670; Correspondence, 1959- 1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Wayfield, Order to Show Cause, May 22, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Wayfield, Rank & File Election Flyers, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Ancewicz, Frank, Hart, Thomas, et. al. v. Local 1292, District Council of Carpenters, Nassau County; 66 Civ. 499 / Docket No. 73-2063; Index, Correspondence, 1962-64, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Trial Committee v. T. Hart, May 17, 1965; Note of Issue, Dec 14, 1966, 1965, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 1967-68, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence to B. Hall, Jan 1, 1969; Order & Judgement, July 2, 1973; Correspondence, 1974, 1969, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Appellate Briefs; Decision, Court of Appeals, May 8, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Local 1292, Election Materials, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Local 1292, Charges v, Tota, R.; Correspondence, Dec 10, 1962; Correspondence, Civil Suit by Members v, Local's Business Agent (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Local 1292, Suit to Remove Officers, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - McCarthy, Lawrence v. Prince Carpentry, Inc.; 77 Civ 2690; Index, Summons; Class Action Complaint, Apr 25 1977; Summons & Complaint, Prince v. L. McCarthy (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Prince; 77 Civ 2690 / 77 Civ 1982; Interrogatories to Prince, May 31, 1977; Motion for Class Action, Je 22, 1977, Memorandum in Opposition, 1977, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Prince; 77 Civ 1982; Judicial Order, July 5, 1977; Motion for Summary Judgement, Dec 12, 1977, 1977, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Prince, Deposition, B. Hall, Jan 16, 1978; Answer to Interrogatories, Mar 22, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Notice of Motion & Affirmation for Partial Summary Judgement, 23-Mar-78, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Deposition, M. Heiberger, Apr 7, 1978; Judicial Opinion, July 19, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Prince Carpentry, Inc., Documents, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Clarke, Eugene v. District Council of Carpenters, Local 608; 81 Civ 5083; Union correspondence to Clarke, Feb 27, 1973; Notice of Trial Committee's Decision, Dec 24, 1980, 1973, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence to International, Jan 19, 1981; Summons & Complaint, Aug 13, 1981; Case Index, Aug 14, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Reply Affidavit, E. Clarke, Sept 24 1981; Deposition, E. Clarke, Dec 16, 1981; Transcript (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Jan 6, 1982; Notice of Motion for Summary Judgement, Apr 16, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Memorandum in Suport of Defendant's Motion, Apr 16, 1982; Notice of Motion, Lack of Service, May 25, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Statement of Facts, Je 1, 1982; Notice & Memorandum in Support of Motion for Re-Argument, Aug. 8, 1982. (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Judgement (Proposed), Sept 8, 1982; Correspondence, B. Hall, Dec 23, 1982; Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Local 608 Constitution & By-Laws; The Rusty Nail, Dec, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Local 608, Internal Charges, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Harte, John v Local 608, Correspondence on Clearance, 1973; Carpenters for a Stronger Union, Literature on Dues Increase, Jan 28, 1983, 1973, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Walsh, Daniel, v. Local 608, Correspondence to Business Agent, 1980; NLRB Charge (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Dwyer, John P. v. Local 1456, Deposition, J. Dwyer; Correspondence, B. Hall to NLRB, Dec 19, 1967; Trial Committee Transcript, Dec 6, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Murphy, Michael v. Local 488; "Committee for Union Justice," "South Bronx Carpenters Association," 1978; Intra-Union Charges, 1979; "Vote for Murphy", 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Maritas, Theodore, District Council of Carpenters, Indictment; NY Carpenters Defense Literature, Jan, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Local 135, Intra-Union Charges, 1967; Local 257, Intra-Union Charges, 1973, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - District Council of Carpenters, Dental Plan Investigation, F. Hogan, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Laborers International Union of North America (LIUNA)
      - Gentile, Joseph v. Plasterers' Tenders' Helpers, Local Union No. 759; New York Civil Court Index No. 37511; Complaint, Jan 6. 1966; Correspondence, 1966-68, 1966, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Ballot, Local 759 Election; Contract, J. Gentile, Business Manager, May 25 1968; Correspondence, Pension Fund (Box 4, Folder 18)